safelite.com 2019-07-09

# Safelite Group Privacy Policy | Safelite

This Privacy Policy explains how we handle the personal information that you provide to us on Web sites controlled by the Safelite Group. This Privacy Policy does not apply to personal information collected from you offline.

## How does this Privacy Policy define "personal information"?

"Personal information" means information that identifies you or could reasonably be used to identify you and which is submitted to and/or collected by Safelite Web sites and maintained by Safelite in an accessible form. Examples of personal information include your name, your postal address and your telephone number.

## How does Safelite collect information online?

Safelite collects information in two ways:

  *  **Personal information you submit:** Safelite collects personal information that you enter into data fields on Safelite Web sites. For example, you may submit your name, postal address, e-mail address, automobile type, insurance carrier and/or other information in order to schedule service, receive information about various subjects, contact Safelite customer service, or respond to Safelite surveys. To protect your privacy, you should not provide Safelite with any information that is not specifically requested.

  *  **Passive collection of unidentifiable information:** Safelite Web sites may collect information about your visits to Safelite Web sites without you actively submitting such information. Unidentifiable information may be collected using various technologies, such as cookies, Internet tags, and web beacons. Your Internet browser automatically transmits to Safelite Web sites some of this unidentifiable information, such as the URL of the Web site you just visited and the browser version your computer is operating. Passive information collection technologies can make your use of Safelite Web sites easier by allowing Safelite to provide better service, customize sites based on consumer preferences, compile statistics, analyze trends, and otherwise administer and improve Safelite Web sites. Certain features of Safelite Web sites may not work without use of passive information collection technologies. Information collected by these technologies cannot be used to identity you without additional identifiable information.

## In what circumstances might Safelite collect and use personal information?

Safelite will use the personal information you provide through Safelite Web sites to respond to your questions and to provide you with efficient customer service. After you have entered personal information into a form or data field on a Safelite Web site, Safelite may use certain identifying technologies to allow that Web site to "remember" your personal preferences, such as sections of that Web site that you visit frequently and, if you choose, your user ID. We may also use this personal information for other business purposes, such as to offer you the opportunity to receive notices regarding Safelite's products or services, to invite you to participate in surveys about our products, or to notify you about special promotions.

Some of our applications and mobile-optimized sites may have location-based features. To deliver these features, we will collect and use location data provided by your mobile device. Location information will be collected solely to deliver the requested feature, and it will not be further retained or stored. By using such applications, you consent to the collection and use of your mobile device location data for purposes of delivering these location-based features.

## Does Safelite consolidate personal information?

Safelite may combine the personal information that you provide to us on one Safelite Web site with the personal information provided by you on other Safelite Web sites. Safelite may also combine personal information that you provide to us online with our offline records as well as records provided by third parties. We use this consolidated information to help us better design Safelite Web sites and Safelite products, to communicate information to you, to enhance our marketing and research activities, and to facilitate other business functions.

## What choices do I have about how Safelite collects and uses personal information about me?

You may always limit the amount and type of personal information that Safelite receives about you by choosing not to enter any personal information into forms or data fields on Safelite Web sites. Some of our online services can only be provided to you if you provide us with appropriate personal information. Other parts of Safelite Web sites may ask whether you wish to opt out or opt into our contact lists for offers, promotions and additional services that may be of interest to you.

Safelite Web sites that use tracking technologies to collect unidentifiable information do not generally provide you with the ability to opt out of the tracking technologies. Some Internet browsers allow you to limit or disable the use of tracking technologies that collect unidentifiable information.

If you no longer wish to receive promotional and marketing emails from Safelite, please click here (https://www.safelite.com/email-unsubscribe).

## How does Safelite use my information in advertising?

Safelite has partnered with companies that deliver ads for our products on sites that you visit on the web. In order to provide you with a more relevant online experience, some of our ads shown to you are based on your previous online activity on our sites and other sites. Information about your online activities, combined with other information, may be used to select an ad for a product or offer that better matches your interests. This advertising practice is called online behavioral advertising (OBA) or interest-based advertising.

To improve our ability to serve you, we may make modifications, improvements, deletions, or amendments to the Web Sites at any time we deem appropriate.  Any and all relevant portions of these Terms of Use will automatically apply to all such modifications, improvements, deletion, and/or amendments as they appear on the Web Sites.

Safelite may use Transcripts, Surveys and Recordings for purposes of performing or delivering a service to you, providing maintenance or support services to you, for training and quality assurance purposes, for purposes of improving our services and for other lawful purposes.

We comply with the requirements of the Digital Advertising Alliance's (DAA) Self-Regulatory Program, whose goal is to provide you with enhanced notice about online advertising practices and choices about the ads you see. You can opt out from receiving ads based on your online behavior either by visiting the DAA opt-out page at <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/> or by clicking on the Ad-Choices icon in or near the ad.

If you elect to opt out of OBA, you will still see ads, but they may not be as relevant to you. Please keep in mind that opting out is cookie-based and will only affect the specific computer and browser on which the opt-out cookie is applied. If you delete your browser cookies or if you use a different computer or different browser and want to continue to be opted out of interest-based advertising, you will need to opt out again.

## How does this site use Google services?

Safelite uses Google Analytics first-party "cookies" and the DoubleClick and other partner third-party "cookies" for reporting and advertising. These first- and third-party cookies are used together to help us better understand your interests and online behavior in an aggregate and anonymous form. The Google Analytics first-party "cookies" are used to compile statistical information and reports on aggregate visitor activity on our website. We use third-party cookies to enable Google Analytics demographics and interest reporting, which allows us to understand, in aggregate, the age, gender, and interests of our visitors. In addition to this, we use first- and third-party Google Analytics, DoubleClick and other partner "cookies" for remarketing. Remarketing allows our ads to be delivered to visitors on other third-party websites after they leave our website. This advertising directly relates to offers that may be of interest to you based on your prior website visit. None of the data we collect from first and third party "cookies" can be linked to an individual person nor is this data able to personally identify any visitor to our website.

If you would like to opt out of Google Analytics tracking, you may do so by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on that can be found here. <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>

## Who will have access to personal information about me?

Personal information can be accessed by a restricted number of Safelite employees, your insurance company if we are processing an insurance claim on your behalf, by certain companies with which Safelite may conduct joint programs, and by individuals and entities with whom Safelite contracts to carry out business activities for Safelite. We train our employees about the importance of privacy and how to handle and manage customer data appropriately and securely. In addition, Safelite's practice is to require its contractors to keep your personal information confidential and to use personal information only to perform functions for Safelite.

## Does Safelite share personal information with third parties?

As a general rule, Safelite does not share your personal information with third parties, unless it is necessary to conduct a joint program or to carry out a program or activity through a contractor. Where required by law, Safelite will not disclose your personal information to third parties for those third parties' marketing purposes, unless you have been provided with an opportunity to opt into or opt out of this disclosure. However, if Safelite sells one of its product lines or divisions, your personal information may be transferred to the buyer so that the buyer can continue to provide you with information and services. If Safelite provides your personal information to individuals and entities which assist us with our business activities, it is Safelite's practice to require those individuals and entities to keep your personal information confidential and to use your personal information only to perform functions for Safelite. Safelite reserves the right to disclose your personal information to respond to authorized information requests from government authorities, to address national security situations, or when otherwise required by law.

## How does Safelite protect personal information?

To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we maintain a layered approach to physical and logical security controls. These measures include fraud screening, computer safeguards, access control and various other controls.

## How does Safelite protect the privacy of children?

Safelite does not knowingly collect or use any personal information from children (we define "children" as minors younger than 13) on Safelite Web sites. We do not knowingly allow children to order our products, communicate with us, or use any of our online services. If you are a parent and become aware that your child has provided us with information, please contact us using one of the methods specified below, and we will work with you to address this issue.

## How may I correct personal information or delete it from current customer records?

You may request to remove your personal information from our current customer records or to amend your personal information. Please notify us of your wishes by contacting us in one of the ways specified below. For our record keeping purposes, we will retain certain personal information you submit in conjunction with commercial transactions.

## How can I contact Safelite?

If you have questions about the use, amendment, or deletion of personal information that you have provided to us, or if you would like to opt out of future communications from a Safelite business or a particular Safelite program, please contact us by clicking on the "Contact us" link on the Web site you are visiting or by e-mailing us at [onlinehelp@safelite.com](mailto:onlinehelp@safelite.com) Alternatively, you may send a letter to the following address:

Safelite Group, Inc.  
Attn. Executive Services  
7400 Safelite Way  
Columbus, Ohio 43235

In all communications to Safelite, please include the e-mail address used (if applicable), the Web site address or the specific Safelite program to which you provided personal information (e.g. Safelite.com, ServiceAutoglass.com, etc.), and a detailed explanation of your request. If you would like to delete or amend your personal information and are contacting us by e-mail, please put "Deletion Request" or "Amendment Request", as applicable, in the subject line of the e-mail. We will do our best to respond to all reasonable requests in a timely manner.

## How will I know whether Safelite has updated this policy?

Safelite reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy without prior notice to reflect technological advancements, legal and regulatory changes and good business practices. If Safelite changes its privacy practices, a new Privacy Policy will reflect those changes and the effective date of the revised Privacy Policy will be set forth in this paragraph. This Privacy Policy was last updated on March 26, 2015 and is effective as of that date. 

For customer assistance and general information, call our toll-free number: [877-664-8931](tel:1-877-664-8931).
